<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Rong&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://rongrg.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Rong&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rongrg.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding LSTM Networks: An Overview of Layers, Cells, Neurons, and Units</title>
      <link>https://rongrg.github.io/posts/2023-02-10-lstm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rongrg.github.io/posts/2023-02-10-lstm/</guid>
      <description>LSTM is a type of recurrent neural network that is widely used in natural language processing, speech recognition, and other applications where sequential data is important. LSTMs are particularly effective at capturing long-term dependencies in sequences of data, which can be challenging for other types of neural networks.
Navigating the jargon associated with the components of LSTM networks can be daunting, even for those familiar with neural networks. Terms like &amp;ldquo;cell,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;layer,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;unit,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;neuron&amp;rdquo; are often thrown around without a clear explanation of their meaning and purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk-sensitive Distributional Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://rongrg.github.io/posts/2022-11-11-riskrl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rongrg.github.io/posts/2022-11-11-riskrl/</guid>
      <description>Reinforcement learning (RL) is a powerful framework for training agents to maximize cumulative reward, but it typically assumes risk-neutrality. This can lead to suboptimal behavior in practical scenarios where the consequences of unfavorable outcomes can be detrimental.
What is risk? Generally, risk might arise whenever there is uncertainty. In a financial situation, investment risk can be identified with uncertain monetary loss. In a safety-critical engineering system, risk is the undesirable detrimental outcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Set Up an RL Project Less Complicated?</title>
      <link>https://rongrg.github.io/posts/2022-05-24-blog-post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rongrg.github.io/posts/2022-05-24-blog-post-1/</guid>
      <description>Setting up an ML envronment can be a tricky thing. Here&amp;rsquo;s what worked for me on how to set up the environment and keep track of experiments.
Project Setup Directory Structure Cookiecuttet
Computational Environment Pycharm virtualenv pip install the packages: [1] Unzip the downloaded mjpro150 into ~/.mujoco/mjpro150, and place the mjkey.txt file at ~/.mujoco/mjkey.txt.
[2] Run pip3 install -U &#39;mujoco-py&amp;lt;1.50.2,&amp;gt;=1.50.1&#39;
[3] Remove ~/.mujoco/mjpro150/bin/libglfw.3.dylib
[4] Run brew install llvm boost hdf5 glfw</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
